<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Midgaard on Theta Nil's Site</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/midgaard/</link><description>Recent content in Midgaard on Theta Nil's Site</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://thetanil.github.io/midgaard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Market Square</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/midgaard/market/square/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/midgaard/market/square/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;You find yourself in Midgaard&amp;rsquo;s bustling Market Square, the commercial heart of the great city. The square teems with activity as merchants, shoppers, and travelers create a vibrant tapestry of city life. Colorful banners flutter overhead, marking different vendor stalls and announcing today&amp;rsquo;s special wares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cobblestone streets radiate outward from the square, worn smooth by countless feet and cart wheels. Market stalls line the square&amp;rsquo;s edges, their wooden frames supporting canvas awnings that provide shade for both merchants and customers. The air is thick with the mingled aromas of fresh bread, exotic spices, leather goods, and the occasional less pleasant scent of livestock.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Temple Square</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/midgaard/temple/square/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/midgaard/temple/square/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;You stand in the heart of Midgaard&amp;rsquo;s Temple Square, the spiritual center of the great city. A magnificent marble fountain dominates the center of the square, its crystalline waters catching the light as they cascade down carved stone tiers. The fountain depicts ancient heroes and divine figures, their faces worn smooth by countless years of weather and the touch of reverent hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stone benches line the square&amp;rsquo;s perimeter, offering rest to weary travelers and contemplative pilgrims. Ornate pillars support covered walkways that provide shelter from sun and rain. To the north, the grand Temple of Midgaard rises majestically, its towering spires reaching toward the heavens. The sound of chanting occasionally drifts down from within.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>